[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":35266,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":715687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":10949,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":726638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":736456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2796,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":739256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4076,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":743335,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1270,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":744607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":748696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1012,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":749711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":752735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 =  2 becaus e 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1486,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":754223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":757224,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":758103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the  first nu mber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":761008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":761991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":765127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":966,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":766095,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":769256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1108,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":770368,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":773032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":895,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":773928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you su btract 6  to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2272,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":776200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":777184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":16973,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":794160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":20592,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":814753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":819297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":820225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2175,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":822401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":695,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":823097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse  of 3 und er +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":825306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":806,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":826114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":828225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":879,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":829106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":13798,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":842906,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4596,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":847506,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":5030,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":852538,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> Ho wever, 2  is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":36432,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":888972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":6854,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":895828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":3687,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":899516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":902229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":9150,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":911380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub >? <br / ><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":913685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":830,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":914516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":917245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":773,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":918020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible. ","rt":20417,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":938438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3468,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":941909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":646,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":942557,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":945117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":952494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":954926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":957134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":16362,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":973497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subtract 9 from it because my result is not larger than 8.","response_history":["5, ","5,","5","5, I got my as","5, I got my answer by adding 4+","5, I got my answer by adding 4 ","5, I got my answer by adding 4","5, I got my answer by adding 1","5, I got my answer by adding 4 +1","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subrat","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 b","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 from it because the number ","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 from it because the ","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 fro m it bec ause the","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 from it because th","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 from it because t","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 from it because my result is not g","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subract 9 from it because my result is not larger than 8.","5, I got my answer by adding 4 + 1 and getting 5, and I don't have to subtract 9 from it because my result is not larger than 8."],"rt":51741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1025240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1029648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"The identity is 0 because anytime the result gets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity.","response_history":["The identy is ","The identity is 0 just like with ","The identity is 0 just like with ","The identity is 0 ","The identity is 0 becaue ","The identity is 0 becaue","The identity is 0 because you ","The identity is 0 because you","The identity is 0 because yo","The identity is 0 because y","The identity is 0 because anytime the na","The identity is 0 because anytime the n","The identity is 0 because anytime the answer gets b","The identity is 0 because anytime the answer gets above 8 it gets subr","The identity is 0 because anytime the answer gets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0 , which  is al","The identity is 0 because anytime the answer gets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is a","The identity is 0 because anytime the answer gets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity.","The identity is 0 because anytime the regets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity.","The identity is 0 because anytime the resgets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity.","The identity is 0 because anytime the resugets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity.","The identity is 0 because anytime the resulgets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity.","The identity is 0 because anytime the result gets above 8 it gets subtracted by 9 to come back to 0, which is called the identity."],"rt":107007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1136657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7713,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1144373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1147525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1154297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>?  Please  explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9 so that you can subtract 9 and get 0.","response_history":["6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 - 9","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 - ","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 -","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 0","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subrt","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subr","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. ","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. t","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a re sult of  9, so 3","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9, so ","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9, so","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9, s","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9, ","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9,","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9 so that you can su btract 9  and get 9","6, This is the answer because 3 + 6 = 9. In this case we would subtract 9 to get 0 as a result. The inverse in this case is whatever gets you a result of 9 so that you can subtract 9 and get 0."],"rt":81540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1235839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. I don't think it's possible to get 1, 3, 5, or 7 from using 2 as a generator.","response_history":["2 is not ","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd resultrs from","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd result","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. S","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. I don't think it's poss ible to  get 1, 3,  5,","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. I don't think it's possible to get 1, 3,  5","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. I don't think it's possible to get 1, 3,  ","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. I don't think it's possible to get 1, 3, 5, or 7 from using  ","No, 2 is not a generator because you can't get odd results from it. I don't think it's possible to get 1, 3, 5, or 7 from using 2 as a generator."],"rt":76652,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1312495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-8 from it as a result. I think you can only get 0, 3, and 6.","response_history":["No,  3 is no t a generator because you can't get 1","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-9 from it. ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-9 from it.","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-9 from it as  ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-9 from it as a result. ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-from it as a result. ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-9from it as a result. ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-from it as a result. ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-8from it as a result. ","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-8 from it as a result. I think you can only get 3 and 6.","No, 3 is not a generator because you can't get all the numbers from 0-8 from it as a result.  I think  you can only get 0, 3, and 6."],"rt":105349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1417847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, 5 is a generator because you can add 5 to itself and get all the numbers from 0-8, you just have to add another 5 each time.","response_history":["Yes, 5 is a generator because you can add 5 to itself and get all the numbers from 0 ","Yes, 5 is a generator because you can add 5 to itself and get all the numbers from 0-8 ","Yes, 5 is a generator because you can add 5 to itself and get all the numbers from 0-8, you just have to add another 5 each tie","Yes, 5 is a generator because you can add 5 to itself and get all the numbers from 0-8, you just have to add another 5 each time."],"rt":29930,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1447780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result from adding 6 to itself.","response_history":["No ","No, 6 is not a generator because Y","No, 6 is not a generator because you a","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0 and 6 as a result ","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0 a","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0 ","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result form su","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result form s","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result form ","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result form","No, 6 is not a genera tor beca use you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result for","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result fo","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result fromas","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result froma","No, 6 is not a generator because you can only get 0, 3, and 6 as a result from adding 6 to itself."],"rt":31169,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1478952,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":9845,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1488800,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"(n-1) + 1","response_history":["The inverse of 1 under +n would be ","1 ","1","(n","(","(n-1) + 1 = -","(n-1) + 1 = 0","(n-1) + 1 = ","(n-1) + 1 =","(n-1) + 1 ","(n-1) + 1","_","(n01","(n0","(n-1","(n-","(n-1) =","(n-1) + 1"],"rt":150314,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1639116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"(n - x) + x, Whatever number n is gets subtracted by whatever number x is. You're left with the inverse that way. So if n is 5 and x is 2, then you would subtract 2 from 5 and be left with 3. So, 3 is the inverse to 2.","response_history":["(n - x) +  x","(n -  x) + ","(n - x) +","(n - x) ","(n - x)","(n - x","(n - ","(n -","(n ","(n 0 ","(n 0","(n - x) + x, My ","(n - x) + x, My","(n - x) + x, M","(n - x) + x, Whatever number n is gets subtracted by whatever number x is. You're left with the inverse that way. So if n is 5 and x is two","(n - x) + x, Whatever number n is gets subtracted by whatever number x is. You're left with the inverse that way. So if n is 5 and x is tw","(n - x) + x, Whatever number n is gets subtracted by whatever number x is. You're left with the inverse that way. So if n is 5 and x is t","(n - x) + x, Whatever number n is gets subtracted by whatever number x is. You're left with the inverse that way. So if n is 5 and x is 2, then you would subtract 2 from 5 and be left with 3. So, 3 is the inverse to 2. ","(n - x) + x, Whatever number n is gets subtracted by whatever number x is. You're left with the inverse that way. So if n is 5 and x is 2, then you would subtract 2 from 5 and be left with 3. So, 3 is th e invers e to 2."],"rt":72728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1711847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I think that pattern will stand always. I think that if n is an odd number then the generator can never be an even number.","response_history":["I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I think that stands ","I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I thin th","I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I thin t","I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I thin ","I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I think that pattern will stand always. I think th at if n  is a ","I think that 1 and 5 are automatically generators, and I think that pattern will stand always. I think that if n is an odd number then the generator can never be an even number."],"rt":50822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1762672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":21823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1784499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":27340,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1811842,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":74889,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1886732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n eventually.","response_history":["Fore","For examp","Th","T","False, ","False,","False. For example, if n =  ","False. For example, if n = 6 then 5 is a geneta","False. For exa mple, if  n = 6 then 5 is a genet","False. For example, if n = 6 then 5 is a generator, but 2 is not","False. For example, if n = 6 ","False. For example, if n = 6","False. For example, if n = 9 and x -","False. For example, if n = 9 and x - ","False. For example, if n = 9 and x -","False. For example, if n = 9 and x = 5 ","False. For example, if n = 9 and x = 5","False. For example, if n = 9 and x = 3 ","False. For example, if n = 9 and x = 3","False. For example, if n = 9 and x = 2","False. For example, if n = 9 and x = 2","True. Since x isn't a di","True. Since x isn't a d","True. Since x isn't a generator then it has to be a ","True. Since x isn't a generator then it divides into n","True. Since x isn't a generator ","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x would y","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x would get you the value of n ","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x would get you the value of n. ","True.  Since x  isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x would get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x towould get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to would get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itwould get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itswould get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itsewould get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itselfwould get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n .","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n e. ","True.  Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n ev.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n eve.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n even.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n event.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n eventu.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n eventual.","True. Since x isn't a generator, then multiple additions of x to itself would get you the value of n eventually."],"rt":217741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2104476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generato r under  +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":33357,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2137836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case both 1 and 2 would be generators since 2 is not a multiple of 5.","response_history":["This is true sometim","Sometimes. I ","Sometimes. I","Sometimes. For examp le 1 is  a ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then we can ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then w","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. 1","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If  ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 4","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certai nly not  be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal t","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and i ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this g","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this cae","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case it would b","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then  x + x w ould = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case it wo","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case i","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case ","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case both 1 and 2 would gb","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4.  If x = 1  and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case both 1 and 2 would g","Sometimes. For example if x = 1 and n = 4 then x + x would = 2. So, 1 is a generator of 4, but 2 would certainly not be since it's a multiple of 4. If x = 1 and n = 5, then x +x would also equal 2 and in this case both 1 and 2 would be generators since 2 is not a multiple of 5."],"rt":139331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2277169,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":60549,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2337723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about yo ur backg round. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2285,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2340011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":3118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2343131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2346995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the mo st advan ced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Trigonometry, Algebra 2, Pre-Calculus","response_history":["Trigonometry, Algebra 2, Geometry","Trigonometry, Algebra 2, Pre-Calculus"],"rt":47408,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2394405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":11421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2405829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":11055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2416887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2420029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do y ou feel  you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":11751,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2431783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2434006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response_history":[],"rt":34,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2434042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What  is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["Egn","Eg","English"],"rt":6690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2440734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, I did not.","response_history":["No, I","No, ","No,","No, I did not."],"rt":10774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2451510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks I usually do. I really liked the challenge and it made me think a lot,  which i s always great. I hope to take part in more HITs soon!","response_history":["Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a ","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the HIT","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the HI","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the H","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks iI","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks i","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks I usually do. I really liked the challenge and the ","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks I usually do. I really liked the challenge and the","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks I usually do. I really liked the challenge  and th","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks I usually do. I really liked the challenge and t","Great HIT! I enjoyed the experience, and this was a lot different from the tasks I usually do. I really liked the challenge and it made me think a lot, which is always great. I hope to take part in more HITs soon!"],"rt":46609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2498121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]